

# CONTACT Phone

#### **Email**

patjdnas@gmail.com

# TRAINING

#### **Coder Academy**

Diploma of Information Technology (WebDev Bootcamp)

#### **Rising Fast Scaffolding**

High Risk Work License, White Card, Senior First Aid

#### **Canadian Forces**

Radio Signals &
Communications Course,
Defensive Driving Course

# SKILLS

# PROFESSIONAL

- Time management
- Problem solving
- Communication (verbal, written, digital & phonetic
- Leadership & managerial
- Ouick learner
- Adaptable
- Attention to detail under pressure
- Team oriented & confident working independently
- Punctual
- Honest

# PATRICK NÖEL

SYDNEY, AUSTRALIA

### **PROFILE**

It is my goal to shift into a challenging role where I have the opportunity to recall, adapt and build upon the skills that I have acquired through previous positions and experiences. I hope to continue to grow professionally while dedicating my focus and wholeheartedly applying myself to the task at hand in an exciting new career. I am currently living in Sydney, Australia and studying a Diploma of Information Technology / Web Development Bootcamp with Coder Academy.

# EXPERIENCE

#### SCAFFOLDER

#### Mr Scaffold | 2020 - 2022

- Working under pressure at heights and in confined spaces, meeting rigid departure deadlines.
- Adhering to strict safety regulations in isolated high security areas such as defence force base & ships.
- Construction & dismantling of scaffold on ADF Navy ships, autonomously and within a team environment.

#### LEAD HAND

# Rising Fast Scaffolding | 2017 - 2020

- Managing teams of up to 10 labourers.
- Adhering to strict safety regulations.
- Client liaison, bookkeeping and job quotations.
- Installation and dismantling of heavy materials under pressure and within strict timeframes.
- Managing worksite timelines and adhoc managerial duties as required.

#### CORPORAL WEAPONS DEBT. (31C)

#### Canadian Forces Infantry | 2009 - 2017

- Organising & managing groups of 6-8 persons.
- Overseeing fire teams & weapons management.
- Small arms coaching & training defence personnel.
- Domestic relief operations (Calgary & Manitoba Floods)
- Transfer to ADF reserves. Honourable release 2017.